And it says replicate writing style.
So we can click on add writing samples, you know,
and sample name.
So this is very cool actually.
Let me explain it to you in simple words.
So let's say that you want to use AI
to write something new, right?
And let's say that you already have written
plenty and plenty of articles or plenty of books
or whatever, you've already written something, right?
And all of us, every single one of us,
have our own literature and have our own style
of writing and style of words, you know?
So we have certain words that we choose to use
when it comes to communicating the meaning
that we want, you know?
And that very style is something for itself.
And what you can do over here is that you can come here
and add your writing samples.
So for example, you can add a single article
that you have already written or something like that.
And by clicking start analysis,
you will be able to have this AI tool and now the sync,
your writing style and now the sync,
the type of words that you use, you know?
And the point here is that when it generates you,
the article, it will generate the article
the way that you would have written it, you know?
It's perfect.
So as I said before,
Jotbot is a very specific AI tool
when it comes to writing and you can see it right now, right?
So it even copies the writing style.
So it will analysis your previous writings
and it will generate you something new based
on that very style that you have in the writing, right?